(upbeat music)
♪ This one is for the boys
with the booming system ♪
♪ Top down, AC with the cooler system ♪
♪ When he come up in the
club, he be blazin' up ♪
♪ Got stacks on deck like he savin' up ♪
♪ And he ill, he real,
he might gotta deal ♪
♪ He pop bottles and he got
the right kind of build ♪
♪ He cold, he dope, he might sell coke ♪
♪ He always in the air,
but he never fly coach ♪
♪ He a motherfuckin' trip,
trip, sailor of the ship, ship ♪
♪ When he make it drip, drip
kiss him on the lip, lip ♪
♪ That's the kind of
dude I was lookin' for ♪
♪ And, yes, you'll get
slapped if you're lookin' ho ♪
♪ I said, excuse me
you're a hell of a guy ♪
♪ I mean my, my, my, my
you're like pelican fly ♪
♪ I mean, you're so shy
and I'm loving your tie ♪
♪ You're like slicker than the guy ♪
♪ With the thing on his eye, oh ♪
♪ Yes, I did, yes, I did ♪
♪ Somebody please tell
him who the eff I is ♪
♪ I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up ♪
♪ Back coupes up and chuck the deuce up ♪
♪ Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ♪
♪ Beating like a drum and
it's coming your way ♪
♪ Can't you hear that ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah that's that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
♪ This one is for the boys in the Polos ♪
♪ Entrepreneur niggas and the moguls ♪
♪ He could ball with the
crew, he could solo ♪
♪ But I think I like him
better when he dolo ♪
♪ And I think I like him
better with the fitted cap on ♪
♪ He ain't even gotta
try to put the mack on ♪
♪ He just gotta give me that
look, when he give me that look ♪
♪ Then them panties comin' off, off, uh ♪
♪ Excuse me, you're a
hell of a guy you know ♪
♪ I really got a thing for American guys ♪
♪ I mean, sigh, sickenin' eyes ♪
♪ I can tell that you're in
touch with your feminine side ♪
♪ Yes, I did, yes, I did ♪
♪ Somebody please tell
him who the eff I is ♪
♪ I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up ♪
♪ Back coupes up and chuck the deuce up ♪
♪ Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ♪
♪ Beating like a drum and
it's coming your way ♪
♪ Can't you hear that ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah that's that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
♪ See, I need you in my
life for me to stay ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, I know you'll stay ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, don't go away, hey ♪
♪ Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ♪
♪ Don't you hear that
heartbeat comin' your way ♪
♪ Oh, it be like ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Can't you hear that boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ♪
♪ Beating like a drum and
it's coming your way ♪
♪ Can't you hear that ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah that's that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪